<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Book Review on Poor Horatio</title>
    <link>/tags/book-review/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Book Review on Poor Horatio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Nick Howard</copyright>
    <atom:link href="/tags/book-review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - The Undoing Project: A Friendship That Changed Our Minds</title>
      <link>/post/the-undoing-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 06:24:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-undoing-project/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Finished &lt;em&gt;The Undoing Project: A Friendship That Changed Our Minds&lt;/em&gt; by Michael Lewis today. Not as good as I hoped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Good&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daniel Kahneman and Amos Tversky had an amazing relationship and it was fascinating to read about it. I read Kahneman&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Thinking, Fast and Slow&lt;/em&gt; a few years ago so I was really looking forward to this book. On top of that I&amp;rsquo;ve a couple of other books by Lewis and always enjoyed them. The parts of the book that focused on the issues that Kahneman and Tversky were finding in the way people think were the most enjoyable. Take five seconds each and give your best estimate of these two problems:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1 x 2 x 3 x 4 x 5 x 6 x 7 x 8&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clear your mind, now try this one:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8 x 7 x 6 x 5 x 4 x 3 x 2 x 1&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s obvious when they are together that you should, assuming the human brain works the way you hope it works, give the same answer. However, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t work that way. Groups given the first problem give a much smaller estimate than groups given the second problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lots of interesting parts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Bad&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite a lot of good, there was also a lot I didn&amp;rsquo;t like. The book felt disjointed. One chapter was about something that happened in the 70s. Then he jumped ahead and was talking about Tversky&amp;rsquo;s relationship with a doctor and a paper from the 90s. Then back to the 70s. I don&amp;rsquo;t necessarily have a problem with that, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t work for Lewis in this case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first chapter, while interesting, had little to do with the rest of the book. The first chapter was basically basketball &lt;em&gt;Moneyball&lt;/em&gt;. The only way it tied into the rest of the book at all was a sentence that said Tversky&amp;rsquo;s last lecture was about basketball. Felt like a reach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I primarily read on a Kindle (I love my Paperwhite) these days, but I read the dead tree edition of this book. A nitpicky thing and maybe most books are this way, but I would prefer to have the chapter name as a running header instead of the author name. I didn&amp;rsquo;t need to see Michael Lewis&amp;rsquo; name on every even numbered page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall the book was decent, but if I had to do it over again I would probably re-read &lt;em&gt;Thinking, Fast and Slow&lt;/em&gt;, or maybe something by Dan Ariely, or even Gerd Gigerenzer&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Calculated Risks&lt;/em&gt;. Gigerenzer was mentioned in the book and had a little kerfuffle with Tversky and, to a lesser extent, Kahneman. They have a different views, but &lt;em&gt;Calculated Risks&lt;/em&gt; is a good book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Verdict - 3 stars&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - The Things They Carried</title>
      <link>/post/the-things-they-carried/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 12:42:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-things-they-carried/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Good - Superb writing. It made me think - a lot. More than just about war.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Bad - I tend to be a non-fiction reader. Maybe it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter if any of what he wrote really happened, but I don&amp;rsquo;t know, I would like to have known what was real and what wasn&amp;rsquo;t. Guess it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Verdict - 4 stars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps because it&amp;rsquo;s the last story and what&amp;rsquo;s closest to my mind now that I&amp;rsquo;ve finished the book, but it made me think about my friend Justin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we got back to school after Christmas break in 2nd grade I remember having a class meeting, of sorts, to say that Justin was sick. He lived around the corner. He lived and breathed baseball. He was Eric Davis among our group. He could hit, he could run, he could throw. He was a joy to be around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Justin&amp;rsquo;s mom made sure we knew that we could still come around as long we weren&amp;rsquo;t sick. So we&amp;rsquo;d go over and hangout. I remember sitting on his back patio with him. His energy was gone. This must have been in the spring. As a 2nd grade kid I never thought about life and death, I didn&amp;rsquo;t know anything about leukemia, never thought about losing a friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The summer between 2nd and 3rd grade we were out playing baseball.  A new glove. An old bat. Green grass. Blue sky. A few puffy white clouds. The hot sun shining down. A friend from across the street comes over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Justin just died.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Hey, let&amp;rsquo;s play some more baseball. That&amp;rsquo;s what Justin would want us to do.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Yeah, he would. Let&amp;rsquo;s play.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I bet he could have played for the Reds.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I know he would have.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Well, right now,&amp;rdquo; she said, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not dead. But when I am, it&amp;rsquo;s like&amp;hellip;I don&amp;rsquo;t know, I guess it&amp;rsquo;s like being inside a book that nobody&amp;rsquo;s reading.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;A book?&amp;rdquo; I said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;An old one. It’s up on a library shelf, so you’re safe and everything, but the book hasn’t been checked out for a long, long time. All you can do is wait. Just hope somebody’ll pick it up and start reading.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If nothing else &lt;em&gt;The Things They Carried&lt;/em&gt; made me pick up Justin&amp;rsquo;s book. For that I am thankful.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - 10% Happier</title>
      <link>/post/10-percent-happier/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 20:03:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/10-percent-happier/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just finished &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/10-Happier-Self-Help-Actually-Works/dp/0062265431/&#34;&gt;10% Happier&lt;/a&gt; by Dan Harris. I give it 3.5 stars, I guess. I rounded down on Goodreads and gave it 3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Good - I like personal stories, hearing about individuals personal struggles, how they overcome them, and how they have found ways to be a better person. As a parent I could use more mindfulness. A lot more mindfulness. It&amp;rsquo;s a struggle. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll start meditating. Anything I can do to help me reason instead of react is a good thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Bad - Short on specifics. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll pick up another book on meditation. Or not. Who knows. With most books like this I feel like they could be shorter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Verdict - 3.5 stars, I guess&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>