<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>book review on Poor Horatio</title>
    <link>http://poorhoratio.com/tags/book-review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in book review on Poor Horatio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 19:28:52 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://poorhoratio.com/tags/book-review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - The Gift of Failure</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-gift-of-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 19:28:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-gift-of-failure/</guid>
      <description>Finished The Gift of Failure: How the Best Parents Learn to Let Go So Their Children Can Succeed by Jessica Lahey.
 The Good
I need daily, maybe hourly, reminders when it comes to parenting. I try to be patient, but it&#39;s hard. There is a lot of good advice in here. It boils down to not doing everything for your kids. Let them fail. Let them learn from those failures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - The Undoing Project: A Friendship That Changed Our Minds</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-undoing-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 06:24:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-undoing-project/</guid>
      <description>Finished The Undoing Project: A Friendship That Changed Our Minds by Michael Lewis today. Not as good as I hoped.
 The Good
Daniel Kahneman and Amos Tversky had an amazing relationship and it was fascinating to read about. I read Kahneman&#39;s Thinking, Fast and Slow a few years ago so I was really looking forward to this book. On top of that I&#39;ve a couple of other books by Lewis and always enjoyed them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - The Things They Carried</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-things-they-carried/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 12:42:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-things-they-carried/</guid>
      <description>The Good - Superb writing. It made me think - a lot. More than just about war.
The Bad - I tend to be a non-fiction reader. Maybe it doesn&#39;t matter if any of what he wrote really happened, but I don&#39;t know, I would like to have known what was real and what wasn&#39;t. Guess it doesn&#39;t matter.
Verdict - 4 stars
 Perhaps because it&#39;s the last story and what&#39;s closest to my mind now that I&#39;ve finished the book, but it made me think about my friend Justin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - 10% Happier</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/10-percent-happier/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 20:03:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/10-percent-happier/</guid>
      <description>Just finished 10% Happier by Dan Harris. I give it 3.5 stars, I guess. I rounded down on Goodreads and gave it 3.
The Good - I like personal stories, hearing about individuals personal struggles, how they overcome them, and how they have found ways to be a better person. As a parent I could use more mindfulness. A lot more mindfulness. It&#39;s a struggle. Maybe I&#39;ll start meditating. Anything I can do to help me reason instead of react is a good thing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>