<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Poor Horatio</title>
    <link>http://poorhoratio.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Poor Horatio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 06:08:20 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://poorhoratio.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandma and Grandad (updated)</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/grandma-and-grandad-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 06:08:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/grandma-and-grandad-2/</guid>
      <description>It&#39;s April 5th, 2020, steeling my voice, I say, &amp;ldquo;Bye, Grandad.&amp;rdquo; He didn&#39;t respond. He couldn&#39;t. My head tells me that&#39;s the last goodbye I&#39;ll tell him. My heart desperately hopes it&#39;s not.
Some people you think, really just hope, will live forever, but time eventually gets the best of us all. Assisted living facilities like where they lived were pretty much locked down at that point. That they let us in to see him at all alarmed me, but I still thought for sure Grandad would bounce back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a world, to have sparrows in it!</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/what-a-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 06:37:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/what-a-world/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;What a world, to have sparrows in it!&amp;rdquo;
That&#39;s a line in Brian Doyle&#39;s A Book of Uncommon Prayer: 100 Celebrations of the Miracle &amp;amp; Muddle of the Ordinary.
The math doesn&#39;t add up, but my favorite chapter title in that book is probably, &amp;ldquo;Prayer for the Elderly Woman on the Train Eating One Almond Every Five Minutes for Two Hours for a Grand Total of Forty Almonds and Believe Me I Counted, Fascinated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Memory</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/my-first-memory/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 06:51:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/my-first-memory/</guid>
      <description>The Writing Life by Annie Dillard, Bird by Bird by Anne Lamott, These Precious Days by Ann Patchett, and, in breaking with the Ann(i)(e) theme, One Long River of Song by Brian Doyle. Brian does end with &amp;ldquo;an&amp;rdquo; though and if we went from Annie-&amp;gt;Anne-&amp;gt;Ann then the next logical name would be An. Anyway, that&#39;s not why I called. If I could wave a magic wand and write like someone, it would be one of those four.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Run-on Sentence About My Mom</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/a-run-on-sentence-about-my-mom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 08:47:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/a-run-on-sentence-about-my-mom/</guid>
      <description>Hallmark movies and presents under the tree and Christmas and the days until pitchers and catchers report and little seedlings peaking their heads above the dirt and covering them up before a frost and telling them to stay warm and blooms opening to show their colors and hummingbirds and bluebirds and mockingbirds and birthdays and Opening Day and other holidays and monarchs and milkweed and Central Pastry and The Jug and Shaddock&#39;s and buying the kids clothes for school and the green tea set that Grandpa bought for Granny and the settee and why did we call it that anyway it sounds kind of pretentious and the hutch and the Christmas cactus that might be a Thanksgiving cactus instead and whatever it is I hope we&#39;re taking good care of it and the little caterpillar watering thing and driving past The Beach Waterpark where I wondered if it was all a dream and the hospital where it was most definitely not a dream and if I&#39;m being honest then sometimes I just want to let out a goddamnit in such a way that people think I&#39;m Les McCann singing Compared to What and Mom would be appalled by that and Grandma too and I&#39;m not proud of it either and I don&#39;t say it out loud but I think it and more than that I feel it and covid and doctors and nurses and December 5th and there are many more things that make me think of my mom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review - The Bedford Boys</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-bedford-boys/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 06:21:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-bedford-boys/</guid>
      <description>“We knew somebody was going to die,” recalled Stevens, “and it wasn’t going to be long.”
 I recently finished Alex Kershaw&#39;s book, The Bedford Boys. I have read a fair number of WWII books over the years and this is one of the best. Highly recommend it.
 JUNE 6, 1944, 12:30 A.M.: The British troopship, the Empire Javelin, steamed steadily across the English Channel. Among her passengers were thirty-four young men from the small Virginia town of Bedford.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts about the last year</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/thoughts-about-the-last-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 06:54:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/thoughts-about-the-last-year/</guid>
      <description>A few thoughts about April 6, 2020 through April 6, 2021.
 Grandma and Grandad Sometimes when I think of Grandma&#39;s struggles the last few years I remember her sitting in her wooden rocking chair at home, she knew her mind and body were failing, and as she gently rocked she twirled her finger to the sky and said, &amp;ldquo;I&#39;m ready to&amp;hellip; check out.&amp;rdquo;
And so on January 20th, Grandma checked out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mom</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/mom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 05:52:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/mom/</guid>
      <description>It was Saturday and only 8:22pm, but I had dozed off on the couch. The buzzing of my phone jarred me awake and by the sound in Dad&#39;s voice I knew it was bad, &amp;ldquo;Nick, the hospital called. Your mother isn&#39;t doing well, if we want to see her, we have to go now. Can you call David?&amp;rdquo;
Only an hour and a half earlier my brother, David, and his wife had called to give us the latest on Mom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview With Grandad</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/interview-with-grandad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 06:40:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/interview-with-grandad/</guid>
      <description>A while back I found the tape of the interview that my wife (then girlfriend), two classmates, and I did with my grandad (that I referenced here). I had it converted to a wav file. Listening to it I can hear in his voice that he did not want to be talking about it. I&#39;m thankful he agreed to it though.
I sure do miss him. Wish I had something like this with my other grandparents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandma and Grandad</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/grandma-and-grandad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 08:13:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/grandma-and-grandad/</guid>
      <description>Steeling my voice, I say, &amp;ldquo;Bye, Grandad.&amp;rdquo; My head tells me that&#39;s the last goodbye I&#39;ll tell him. My heart desperately hopes it&#39;s not.
Some people you think, really just hope, will live forever, but time eventually gets the best of us all. They let us into the assisted living facility to see him. That they were allowing us to go in at all alarmed me, but I still thought for sure Grandad would bounce back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandma is Gone</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/grandma-is-gone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 19:54:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/grandma-is-gone/</guid>
      <description>“Grandma is gone”
That’s what the text said anyway. Truth be told, she had been gone at least a little while. And on the slow, sad road longer than that. A few years ago, or maybe it was more, I really don’t remember, she was in the hospital and as I walked in to her room she greeted me, “Hello Nick-a-roo.”
That is the last time I remember her remembering me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - The Brothers Karamazov</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-brothers-karamazov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 19:26:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-brothers-karamazov/</guid>
      <description>Finally finished The Brothers Karamazov by Fyodor Dostoyevsky. I read the Pevear translation. It took forever. That was a long book.
 The Good
The Pevear translation seems to be regarded as the most true to the original. I have no idea if that is true or not, I don&#39;t read Russian. The story is intriguing, the characters are complex, and it makes you think.
 The Bad
This was a tough read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Met My Wife at Arby&#39;s</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/how-i-met-my-wife-at-arbys/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 14:39:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/how-i-met-my-wife-at-arbys/</guid>
      <description>At work there is a group that puts on fun events for our team called the Fun Police. For Valentine&#39;s Day I wrote about how I met my wife. I had fun writing it up and thought I would share it here. Feel free to use it as a guide to meeting your own wife at Arby&#39;s. Our Arby&#39;s sign didn&#39;t look like this one, but it should have.
 Let’s turn back the clock to August 1995&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - The Gift of Failure</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-gift-of-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 19:28:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-gift-of-failure/</guid>
      <description>Finished The Gift of Failure: How the Best Parents Learn to Let Go So Their Children Can Succeed by Jessica Lahey.
 The Good
I need daily, maybe hourly, reminders when it comes to parenting. I try to be patient, but it&#39;s hard. There is a lot of good advice in here. It boils down to not doing everything for your kids. Let them fail. Let them learn from those failures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - The Undoing Project: A Friendship That Changed Our Minds</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-undoing-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 06:24:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-undoing-project/</guid>
      <description>Finished The Undoing Project: A Friendship That Changed Our Minds by Michael Lewis today. Not as good as I hoped.
 The Good
Daniel Kahneman and Amos Tversky had an amazing relationship and it was fascinating to read about. I read Kahneman&#39;s Thinking, Fast and Slow a few years ago so I was really looking forward to this book. On top of that I&#39;ve a couple of other books by Lewis and always enjoyed them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - The Things They Carried</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-things-they-carried/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 12:42:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-things-they-carried/</guid>
      <description>The Good - Superb writing. It made me think - a lot. More than just about war.
The Bad - I tend to be a non-fiction reader. Maybe it doesn&#39;t matter if any of what he wrote really happened, but I don&#39;t know, I would like to have known what was real and what wasn&#39;t. Guess it doesn&#39;t matter.
Verdict - 4 stars
 Perhaps because it&#39;s the last story and what&#39;s closest to my mind now that I&#39;ve finished the book, but it made me think about my friend Justin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - 10% Happier</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/10-percent-happier/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 20:03:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/10-percent-happier/</guid>
      <description>Just finished 10% Happier by Dan Harris. I give it 3.5 stars, I guess. I rounded down on Goodreads and gave it 3.
The Good - I like personal stories, hearing about individuals personal struggles, how they overcome them, and how they have found ways to be a better person. As a parent I could use more mindfulness. A lot more mindfulness. It&#39;s a struggle. Maybe I&#39;ll start meditating. Anything I can do to help me reason instead of react is a good thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Favorite 2016 Books</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/2016-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 20:45:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/2016-books/</guid>
      <description>A few years ago I started reading a lot more and keeping track of what I&#39;m reading. I&#39;m a big fan of Goodreads. Anyway, something else I like are &amp;ldquo;best books I read this year (or last, as it were)&amp;rdquo; lists. So here is mine, in no particular order, except my favorite is first.
 Shoe Dog by Phil Knight  Fantastic book about the beginning of Nike. I don&#39;t care much about shoes, but I remember having Nike shoes in elementary school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 12:33:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/about/</guid>
      <description>The name of this site is derived from the episode of The Andy Griffith Show where Opie says &amp;ldquo;Poor Horatio&amp;rdquo; in reference to, what he believes is, half a boy.
  You can find me on Twitter dot com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World (again)</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/hello-world-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 17:19:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/hello-world-again/</guid>
      <description>Let&#39;s see how many times in the next year I post something. I&#39;ll put the over/under at 2.5, not including this one.
So, the setup I am currently using is:
 Hover.com (domain registration) Cloudflare (DNS) Hugo (static site generator) Github pages  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>