<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Poor Horatio</title>
    <link>/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Poor Horatio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Nick Howard</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 19:54:51 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandma is Gone</title>
      <link>/2018/03/29/granda-is-gone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 19:54:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/29/granda-is-gone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;“Grandma is gone”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s what the text said anyway. Truth be told, she had been gone at least a little while. And on the slow, sad road longer than that. A few years ago, or maybe it was more, I really don’t remember, she was in the hospital and as I walk in to her room she greets me, “Hello Nick-a-roo.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is the last time I remember her remembering me. Man, I hope I never get Alzheimer’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grandma and Grandpa always lived nearby when I was a kid. My brother and I spent a lot of time there. The first house I remember was a ranch with a basement. I don’t know what the reality was, but I remember the basement being filled with electronics that my grandpa would work on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then they moved to an apartment with a pool. Hanging out at the pool with the two of them was a lot of fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The back room of that apartment was the tv room. Also in that room was a roll top desk that housed a Commodore 64. “The Train: Escape to Normandy” had to be my favorite game. Never could finish it though. It always got stuck on a bridge and then you would have to restart. That didn’t stop us from playing again and again thinking that the next time would be the time you would make it past.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From there they moved to a condo around the corner from where we lived. I must have walked over there a thousand times. Going over to play games on the computer, watch tv, eat some junk food and drink pop, or to help clean. My brother started helping Grandma first and when he moved on to a real job I took over. There aren’t many jobs better than cleaning for your grandma, eating brownies, talking to your grandpa, and getting paid to do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through the years we took a trip to Disney World. Ate at Bill Knapp’s for birthdays. Had fantastic Christmas after fantastic Christmas. Went school shopping. Spent time at the campground in their little camper. Went to Ray’s Barber Shop for haircuts. Played a lot of golf with Grandpa. Grandpa had bypass surgery in there too. Somehow he ended up with a t-shirt out of the surgery and recovery. The most expensive t-shirt he ever bought he told me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those are memories I’ll treasure forever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the time you realize your grandparents have an interesting story to tell it’s too late to hear that story. I wish I would have asked her more questions about growing up in the 30s. About her experiences in the 40s. Stories about meeting my grandpa. Stories about raising my mom and uncle. As I get older my favorite part of talking to people is hearing their stories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grandma would always get emotional when she would talk about her family. She had six siblings. One of her brothers was two years older than her. I don’t know if he enlisted or was drafted into the Army. Regardless, in January 1945 he was in the Philippines. On January 27th he was killed in action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first letter home from a commanding officer, addressed to their mother, says, “in the face of machine gun fire from dug in Japanese tanks and gun positions, your son was killed instantly by a burst of this machine gun fire.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next letter states, “At that time Pfc Lindsay was instantly killed by a mortar shell that fell close by.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Either way, her brother was dead. By May her mother was dead. And in January 1949 her father died. In the span of four years she lost one of her brothers and both of her parents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m not sure Grandma ever got over losing her brother.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grandpa grew up in Kentucky. I’m not sure when he ended up in Ohio. I think I know even less about his story. He was a chemist at the steel mill. He was in the Navy when he and Grandma got married.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In late 1995 we found out that Grandpa was sick. By June he was gone. Gone to leukemia. He had not yet reached 70. He bought me and my brother a Nintendo and a little tv one Christmas. He took us to Reds games. He was funny, patient, kind, quiet, and smart. I still miss him terribly. He was, unquestionably, one of my favorite people ever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just thinking of Grandpa now I still get a little misty eyed. I think of walking backwards to the pool. I think of a rainy night in Cincinnati when we went to the Reds game. I can picture being in his Oldsmobile driving on I-75 listening listening to Marty and Joe doing the post game show with lightning all around. When he was sick I remember he scratched himself on something and seemed to be bleeding a lot. I asked if he was okay. I was worried. He kind of chuckled and smiled. Looking back it was the smile of someone that knew he was near the end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s funny the things we remember about significant events in our lives. It was a hot day when Grandpa was buried. I distinctly remember being uncomfortable wearing a tie with a short-sleeved shirt. I sat close to my two younger cousins during the service. The older of the two said, “Grandpa is in heaven now.” The younger one replied, “I think Grandpa is in that box.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Five years after Grandpa died Grandma remarried. A retired Marine, my step-grandfather is one of the finest men I’ve ever known. At first they lived in a house in a retirement center. Eventually that got to be too much and they moved into an apartment in the nursing home. He is still there, but as Grandma’s condition worsened she moved to a room where she could get more care. It would have been easy at the end to give up on her, but he would shuffle with his walker down the long hall at the nursing home from his apartment to see her.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grandma has been gone just over a month now. This wasn’t meant to be sad. I just wanted to take a few minutes and write a little about. I am thankful I was able to spend as much time with Grandma as I did. I will be forever grateful for both of my grandparents and my step-grandpa. They had an impact on my life that I cannot put into words.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - The Brothers Karamazov</title>
      <link>/2017/03/05/the-brothers-karamazov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 19:26:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/05/the-brothers-karamazov/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Finally finished &lt;em&gt;The Brothers Karamazov&lt;/em&gt; by Fyodor Dostoyevsky. I read the Pevear translation. It took forever. That was a long book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Good&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Pevear translation seems to be regarded as the most true to the original. I have no idea if that is true or not, I don&amp;rsquo;t read Russian. The story is intriguing, the characters are complex, and it makes you think.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Bad&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a tough read. Maybe I should have read the McDuff translation? I don&amp;rsquo;t know. I almost gave up around 10% in. To be honest, the first 40-50% of the book dragged on. There were paragraphs that ran pages. I wonder if it&amp;rsquo;s like that in the original. The second half was more enjoyable. It seemed a little faster paced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A fair number of people read this and it seems to have a life altering impact. I didn&amp;rsquo;t get that from it. One of these days maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll read it again and pause and reflect more. When I hit the halfway mark I was ready to be done with it. Probably not the best attitude to have. If I do read it again it would be a good one for a book club or a group to discuss what&amp;rsquo;s happening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Verdict&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a classic, right? I wrote a lot more bad than good, but I still give it 4 stars.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Met My Wife at Arby&#39;s</title>
      <link>/2017/02/12/how-i-met-my-wife-at-arbys/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 14:39:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/02/12/how-i-met-my-wife-at-arbys/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At work there is a group that puts on fun events for our team called the Fun Police. For Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day I wrote about how I met my wife. I had fun writing it up and thought I would share it here. Feel free to use it as a guide to meeting your own wife at Arby&amp;rsquo;s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s turn back the clock to August 1995&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the corner of a busy street in my hardscrabble town sits an Arby’s. When the traffic dies down at night and you listen closely you can hear the din of steel being made. Anyway, the interesting thing about this particular Arby’s is that to get to the dining room you walk down a little ramp. Who doesn’t love Arby’s? Maybe not the lady that tripped on the rug going down the ramp. That will probably taint your Arby’s experience. Everyone else loves Arby’s though. Especially when you can get 5 roast beef or beef ‘n cheddar sandwiches for $5. What a time to be alive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I work at Arby’s and have since February. I make $4.30/hour. I&amp;rsquo;m wearing black shoes, black pants, an aqua shirt, black apron, and a black hat. In other words, I’m making bank and looking good. Oh yeah.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a hot Saturday in early August and I walk in, “Hey Steve!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Steve is the affable assistant manager at Arby’s. Not like Jack. Jack is the manager and he is the opposite of affable. So, I’m slinging roast beef. Actually, I lied, I’m not slinging roast beef. You have to be 18 to touch the slicer and I’m only 16.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m working the front counter and in walks a new employee. A girl about my age. “Well, hello,” I think to myself and then finish getting the curly fries and Jamocha shake I was working on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A week or two have passed. With these hot August days it’s hard to keep track of time. I’ve decided I should ask the new girl if she wants to go out sometime. Lisa. Lisa is her name. Turns out she has one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m in the drive thru. She’s by one of the front registers and it’s not busy. I’m nervous. Hopefully it’s not obvious. I’m pretty sure it’s obvious. It’s hot. I’m sweating. She’s going to say no. I know it. Doesn’t this place of AC? Have mercy, Jack, would it kill you to keep it a degree or two cooler in this joint?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I finally summon the courage, walk over, and, recalling a favorite Tom and Jerry episode, look at her and say, &amp;ldquo;You set my soul on fire. It is not just a little spark. It is a flame. A big, roaring flame.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, that&amp;rsquo;s not true at all. Channeling my inner Butthead I ask, &amp;ldquo;Would you like to, uh, go out with me sometime? Or something. Cause that would be cool and stuff.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have caught her in a moment of desperation! She says, &amp;ldquo;Yes.&amp;rdquo; Unbelievable! It’s a miracle!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Married now for going on 16 years and I’m still punching above my weight. Maybe next time I&amp;rsquo;ll tell you about how I forgot my socks on our wedding day. And as it would turn out, I also forgot my pants.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - The Gift of Failure</title>
      <link>/2017/01/31/the-gift-of-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 19:28:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/31/the-gift-of-failure/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Finished &lt;em&gt;The Gift of Failure: How the Best Parents Learn to Let Go So Their Children Can Succeed&lt;/em&gt; by Jessica Lahey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Good&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I need daily, maybe hourly, reminders when it comes to parenting. I try to be patient, but it&amp;rsquo;s hard. There is a lot of good advice in here. It boils down to not doing everything for your kids. Let them fail. Let them learn from those failures. Probably good advice for adults too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I especially enjoyed the beginning that talked about how society used to view children as miniature adults. It made me think. Of course, kids also used to work in factories. It&amp;rsquo;s probably best that we&amp;rsquo;ve moved on from that. However, it does show that kids are capable of more than what we think (or they think).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Bad&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seemed to get a little repetitive. I felt like I got the point, but it was probably good to have it hammered in again (and again).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Verdict&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4 stars. I&amp;rsquo;d probably read &lt;em&gt;Mindset: The New Psychology of Success&lt;/em&gt; before this one, definitely worth reading though.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - The Undoing Project: A Friendship That Changed Our Minds</title>
      <link>/2017/01/16/the-undoing-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 06:24:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/16/the-undoing-project/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Finished &lt;em&gt;The Undoing Project: A Friendship That Changed Our Minds&lt;/em&gt; by Michael Lewis today. Not as good as I hoped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Good&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daniel Kahneman and Amos Tversky had an amazing relationship and it was fascinating to read about. I read Kahneman&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Thinking, Fast and Slow&lt;/em&gt; a few years ago so I was really looking forward to this book. On top of that I&amp;rsquo;ve a couple of other books by Lewis and always enjoyed them. The parts of the book that focused on the issues that Kahneman and Tversky were finding in the way people think were the most enjoyable. Take five seconds each and give your best estimate of these two problems:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1 x 2 x 3 x 4 x 5 x 6 x 7 x 8&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clear your mind, now try this one:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8 x 7 x 6 x 5 x 4 x 3 x 2 x 1&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s obvious when they are together that you should, assuming the human brain works the way you hope it works, give the same answer. However, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t work that way. Groups given the first problem give a much smaller estimate than groups given the second problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lots of interesting parts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Bad&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite a lot of good, there was also a lot I didn&amp;rsquo;t like. The book felt disjointed. One chapter was about something that happened in the 70s. Then he jumped ahead and was talking about Tversky&amp;rsquo;s relationship with a doctor and a paper from the 90s. Then back to the 70s. I don&amp;rsquo;t necessarily have a problem with that, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t work for Lewis in this case.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first chapter, while interesting, had little to do with the rest of the book. The first chapter was basically basketball &lt;em&gt;Moneyball&lt;/em&gt;. The only way it tied into the rest of the book at all was a sentence that said Tversky&amp;rsquo;s last lecture was about basketball. Felt like a reach.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I primarily read on a Kindle (I love my Paperwhite) these days, but I read the dead tree edition of this book. A nitpicky thing and maybe most books are this way, but I would prefer to have the chapter name as a running header instead of the author name. I didn&amp;rsquo;t need to see Michael Lewis&amp;rsquo; name on every even numbered page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall the book was decent, but if I had to do it over again I would probably re-read &lt;em&gt;Thinking, Fast and Slow&lt;/em&gt;, or maybe something by Dan Ariely, or even Gerd Gigerenzer&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em&gt;Calculated Risks&lt;/em&gt;. Gigerenzer was mentioned in the book and had a little kerfuffle with Tversky and, to a lesser extent, Kahneman. They have a different view of things, but &lt;em&gt;Calculated Risks&lt;/em&gt; is a good book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Verdict - 3 stars&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - The Things They Carried</title>
      <link>/2017/01/08/the-things-they-carried/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 12:42:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/08/the-things-they-carried/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Good - Superb writing. It made me think - a lot. More than just about war.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Bad - I tend to be a non-fiction reader. Maybe it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter if any of what he wrote really happened, but I don&amp;rsquo;t know, I would like to have known what was real and what wasn&amp;rsquo;t. Guess it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Verdict - 4 stars&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps because it&amp;rsquo;s the last story and what&amp;rsquo;s closest to my mind now that I&amp;rsquo;ve finished the book, but it made me think about my friend Justin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we got back to school after Christmas break in 2nd grade I remember having a class meeting, of sorts, to say that Justin was sick. He lived around the corner. He lived and breathed baseball. He was Eric Davis among our group. He could hit, he could run, he could throw. He was a joy to be around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Justin&amp;rsquo;s mom made sure we knew that we could still come around as long we weren&amp;rsquo;t sick. So we&amp;rsquo;d go over and hangout. I remember sitting on his back patio with him. His energy was gone. This must have been in the spring. As a 2nd grade kid I never thought about life and death, I didn&amp;rsquo;t know anything about leukemia, never thought about losing a friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The summer between 2nd and 3rd grade we were out playing baseball.  A new glove. An old bat. Green grass. Blue sky. A few puffy white clouds. The hot sun shining down. A friend from across the street comes over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Justin just died.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Hey, let&amp;rsquo;s play some more baseball. That&amp;rsquo;s what Justin would want us to do.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Yeah, he would. Let&amp;rsquo;s play.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I bet he could have played for the Reds.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I know he would have.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Well, right now,&amp;rdquo; she said, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not dead. But when I am, it&amp;rsquo;s like&amp;hellip;I don&amp;rsquo;t know, I guess it&amp;rsquo;s like being inside a book that nobody&amp;rsquo;s reading.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;A book?&amp;rdquo; I said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;An old one. It’s up on a library shelf, so you’re safe and everything, but the book hasn’t been checked out for a long, long time. All you can do is wait. Just hope somebody’ll pick it up and start reading.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If nothing else &lt;em&gt;The Things They Carried&lt;/em&gt; made me pick up Justin&amp;rsquo;s book. For that I am thankful.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - 10% Happier</title>
      <link>/2017/01/05/10-percent-happier/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 20:03:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/05/10-percent-happier/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just finished &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/10-Happier-Self-Help-Actually-Works/dp/0062265431/&#34;&gt;10% Happier&lt;/a&gt; by Dan Harris. I give it 3.5 stars, I guess. I rounded down on Goodreads and gave it 3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Good - I like personal stories, hearing about individuals personal struggles, how they overcome them, and how they have found ways to be a better person. As a parent I could use more mindfulness. A lot more mindfulness. It&amp;rsquo;s a struggle. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll start meditating. Anything I can do to help me reason instead of react is a good thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Bad - Short on specifics. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll pick up another book on meditation. Or not. Who knows. With most books like this I feel like they could be shorter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Verdict - 3.5 stars, I guess&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Favorite 2016 Books</title>
      <link>/2017/01/04/2016-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 20:45:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/04/2016-books/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A few years ago I started reading a lot more and keeping track of what I&amp;rsquo;m reading. I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of &lt;a href=&#34;http://goodreads.com&#34;&gt;Goodreads&lt;/a&gt;. Anyway, something else I like are &amp;ldquo;best books I read this year (or last, as it were)&amp;rdquo; lists. So here is mine, in no particular order, except my favorite is first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shoe Dog by Phil Knight&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fantastic book about the beginning of Nike. I don&amp;rsquo;t care much about shoes, but I remember having Nike shoes in elementary school. Then in 4th grade I got a pair of Reeboks and they fell apart before the end of the year. It&amp;rsquo;s been Nike ever since.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pear Shaped: The Funniest Book So Far This Year About Brain Cancer by Adam Blain&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A funny book about a not funny subject.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inside Delta Force by Eric Haney&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A look at the start of Delta Force. I especially enjoyed hearing his perspective on what happened in Iran during the failed hostage rescue mission.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Last Train to Paradise by Les Standiford&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn&amp;rsquo;t give this book a five star review, but looking back I wonder if I should have. Who is a modern day Henry Flagler? Anyone?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Devotion: An Epic Story of Heroism, Friendship, and Sacrifice by Adam Makos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amazing Korean War story.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 12:33:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The name of this site is derived from the episode of &lt;em&gt;The Andy Griffith Show&lt;/em&gt; where Opie says &amp;ldquo;Poor Horatio&amp;rdquo; in reference to, what he believes, is half a boy.
&lt;iframe width=&#34;540&#34; height=&#34;383&#34; src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/gGrL5C4uS1s&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can find me on &lt;a href=&#34;http://twitter.com/nickhoward&#34;&gt;Twitter dot com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World (again)</title>
      <link>/2017/01/02/hello-world-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 17:19:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/01/02/hello-world-again/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s see how many times in the next year I post something. I&amp;rsquo;ll put the over/under at 2.5, not including this one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, the setup I am currently using is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hover.com (domain registration)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cloudflare (DNS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hugo (static site generator)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Github pages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>