<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Book Review on Poor Horatio</title>
    <link>/categories/book-review/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Book Review on Poor Horatio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Nick Howard</copyright>
    <atom:link href="/categories/book-review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - The Brothers Karamazov</title>
      <link>/2017/03/05/the-brothers-karamazov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 19:26:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/03/05/the-brothers-karamazov/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Finally finished &lt;em&gt;The Brothers Karamazov&lt;/em&gt; by Fyodor Dostoyevsky. I read the Pevear translation. It took forever. That was a long book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Good&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Pevear translation seems to be regarded as the most true to the original. I have no idea if that is true or not, I don&amp;rsquo;t read Russian. The story is intriguing, the characters are complex, and it makes you think.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Bad&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a tough read. Maybe I should have read the McDuff translation? I don&amp;rsquo;t know. I almost gave up around 10% in. To be honest, the first 40-50% of the book dragged on. There were paragraphs that ran pages. I wonder if it&amp;rsquo;s like that in the original. The second half was more enjoyable. It seemed a little faster paced.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A fair number of people read this and it seems to have a life altering impact. I didn&amp;rsquo;t get that from it. One of these days maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll read it again and pause and reflect more. When I hit the halfway mark I was ready to be done with it. Probably not the best attitude to have. If I do read it again it would be a good one for a book club or a group to discuss what&amp;rsquo;s happening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Verdict&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a classic, right? I wrote a lot more bad than good, but I still give it 4 stars.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>