<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Poor Horatio</title>
    <link>http://poorhoratio.com/post/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Poor Horatio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Nick Howard</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 12:42:35 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://poorhoratio.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - The Things They Carried</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/2017/01/08/the-things-they-carried/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 12:42:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/2017/01/08/the-things-they-carried/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Good - Superb writing. It made me think - a lot. More than just about war.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Bad - I tend to be a non-fiction reader. Maybe it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter if any of what he wrote really happened, but I don&amp;rsquo;t know, I would like to have known what was real and what wasn&amp;rsquo;t. Guess it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Perhaps because it&amp;rsquo;s the last story and what&amp;rsquo;s closest to my mind now that I&amp;rsquo;ve finished the book, but it made me think about my friend Justin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we got back to school after Christmas break in 2nd grade I remember having a class meeting, of sorts, to say that Justin was sick. He lived around the corner. He lived and breathed baseball. He was Eric Davis among our group. He could hit, he could run, he could throw. He was a joy to be around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Justin&amp;rsquo;s mom made sure we knew that we could still come around as long we weren&amp;rsquo;t sick. So we&amp;rsquo;d go over and hangout. I remember sitting on his back patio with him. His energy was gone. This must have been in the spring. As a 2nd grade kid I never thought about life and death, I didn&amp;rsquo;t know anything about leukemia, never thought about losing a friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The summer between 2nd and 3rd grade we were out playing baseball.  A new glove. An old bat. Green grass. Blue sky. A few puffy white clouds. The hot sun shining down. A friend from across the street comes over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Justin just died.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Hey, let&amp;rsquo;s play some more baseball. That&amp;rsquo;s what Justin would want us to do.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Yeah, he would. Let&amp;rsquo;s play.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I bet he could have played for the Reds.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I know he would have.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Well, right now,&amp;rdquo; she said, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not dead. But when I am, it&amp;rsquo;s like&amp;hellip;I don&amp;rsquo;t know, I guess it&amp;rsquo;s like being inside a book that nobody&amp;rsquo;s reading.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;A book?&amp;rdquo; I said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;An old one. It’s up on a library shelf, so you’re safe and everything, but the book hasn’t been checked out for a long, long time. All you can do is wait. Just hope somebody’ll pick it up and start reading.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If nothing else &lt;em&gt;The Things They Carried&lt;/em&gt; made me pick up Justin&amp;rsquo;s book. For that I am thankful.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - 10% Happier</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/2017/01/05/10-percent-happier/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 20:03:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/2017/01/05/10-percent-happier/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just finished &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.amazon.com/10-Happier-Self-Help-Actually-Works/dp/0062265431/&#34;&gt;10% Happier&lt;/a&gt; by Dan Harris. I give it 3.5 stars, I guess. I rounded down on Goodreads and gave it 3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Good - I like personal stories, hearing about individuals personal struggles, how they overcome them, and how they have found ways to be a better person. As a parent I could use more mindfulness. A lot more mindfulness. It&amp;rsquo;s a struggle. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll start meditating. Anything I can do to help me reason instead of react is a good thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Bad - Short on specifics. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll pick up another book on meditation. Or not. Who knows. With most books like this I feel like they could be shorter.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Favorite 2016 Books</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/2017/01/04/2016-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 20:45:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/2017/01/04/2016-books/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A few years ago I started reading a lot more and keeping track of what I&amp;rsquo;m reading. I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of &lt;a href=&#34;http://goodreads.com&#34;&gt;Goodreads&lt;/a&gt;. Anyway, something else I like are &amp;ldquo;best books I read this year (or last, as it were)&amp;rdquo; lists. So here is mine, in no particular order, except my favorite is first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shoe Dog by Phil Knight&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fantastic book about the beginning of Nike. I don&amp;rsquo;t care much about shoes, but I remember having Nike shoes in elementary school. Then in 4th grade I got a pair of Reeboks and they fell apart before the end of the year. It&amp;rsquo;s been Nike ever since.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pear Shaped: The Funniest Book So Far This Year About Brain Cancer by Adam Blain&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A funny book about a not funny subject.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inside Delta Force by Eric Haney&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A look at the start of Delta Force. I especially enjoyed hearing his perspective on what happened in Iran during the failed hostage rescue mission.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Last Train to Paradise by Les Standiford&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I didn&amp;rsquo;t give this book a five star review, but looking back I wonder if I should have. Who is a modern day Henry Flagler? Anyone?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Devotion: An Epic Story of Heroism, Friendship, and Sacrifice by Adam Makos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Amazing Korean War story.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World (again)</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/2017/01/02/hello-world-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 17:19:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/2017/01/02/hello-world-again/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s see how many times in the next year I post something. I&amp;rsquo;ll put the over/under at 2.5, not including this one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, the setup I am currently using is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hover.com (domain registration)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cloudflare (DNS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hugo (static site generator)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Github pages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>