<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Poor Horatio</title>
    <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Poor Horatio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 06:40:23 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://poorhoratio.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview With Grandad</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/interview-with-grandad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 06:40:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/interview-with-grandad/</guid>
      <description>A while back I found the tape of the interview that my wife (then girlfriend), two classmates, and I did with my grandad. I had it converted to a wav file. Listening to it I can hear in his voice that he did not want to be talking about it. I&#39;m thankful he agreed to it though.
I sure do miss him. Wish I had something like this with my other grandparents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandma and Grandad</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/grandma-and-grandad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2020 08:13:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/grandma-and-grandad/</guid>
      <description>Steeling my voice, I say, &amp;ldquo;Bye, Grandad.&amp;rdquo; My head tells me that&#39;s the last goodbye I&#39;ll tell him. My heart desperately hopes it&#39;s not.
Some people you think, really just hope, will live forever, but time eventually gets the best of us all. They let us into the assisted living facility to see him. That they were allowing us to go in at all alarmed me, but I still thought for sure Grandad would bounce back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandma is Gone</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/grandma-is-gone/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Mar 2018 19:54:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/grandma-is-gone/</guid>
      <description>“Grandma is gone”
That’s what the text said anyway. Truth be told, she had been gone at least a little while. And on the slow, sad road longer than that. A few years ago, or maybe it was more, I really don’t remember, she was in the hospital and as I walk in to her room she greets me, “Hello Nick-a-roo.”
That is the last time I remember her remembering me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - The Brothers Karamazov</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-brothers-karamazov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 19:26:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-brothers-karamazov/</guid>
      <description>Finally finished The Brothers Karamazov by Fyodor Dostoyevsky. I read the Pevear translation. It took forever. That was a long book.
 The Good
The Pevear translation seems to be regarded as the most true to the original. I have no idea if that is true or not, I don&#39;t read Russian. The story is intriguing, the characters are complex, and it makes you think.
 The Bad
This was a tough read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Met My Wife at Arby&#39;s</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/how-i-met-my-wife-at-arbys/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 14:39:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/how-i-met-my-wife-at-arbys/</guid>
      <description>At work there is a group that puts on fun events for our team called the Fun Police. For Valentine&#39;s Day I wrote about how I met my wife. I had fun writing it up and thought I would share it here. Feel free to use it as a guide to meeting your own wife at Arby&#39;s. Our Arby&#39;s sign didn&#39;t look like this one, but it should have.
 Let’s turn back the clock to August 1995&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - The Gift of Failure</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-gift-of-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 19:28:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-gift-of-failure/</guid>
      <description>Finished The Gift of Failure: How the Best Parents Learn to Let Go So Their Children Can Succeed by Jessica Lahey.
 The Good
I need daily, maybe hourly, reminders when it comes to parenting. I try to be patient, but it&#39;s hard. There is a lot of good advice in here. It boils down to not doing everything for your kids. Let them fail. Let them learn from those failures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - The Undoing Project: A Friendship That Changed Our Minds</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-undoing-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 06:24:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-undoing-project/</guid>
      <description>Finished The Undoing Project: A Friendship That Changed Our Minds by Michael Lewis today. Not as good as I hoped.
 The Good
Daniel Kahneman and Amos Tversky had an amazing relationship and it was fascinating to read about. I read Kahneman&#39;s Thinking, Fast and Slow a few years ago so I was really looking forward to this book. On top of that I&#39;ve a couple of other books by Lewis and always enjoyed them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - The Things They Carried</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-things-they-carried/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 12:42:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/the-things-they-carried/</guid>
      <description>The Good - Superb writing. It made me think - a lot. More than just about war.
The Bad - I tend to be a non-fiction reader. Maybe it doesn&#39;t matter if any of what he wrote really happened, but I don&#39;t know, I would like to have known what was real and what wasn&#39;t. Guess it doesn&#39;t matter.
Verdict - 4 stars
 Perhaps because it&#39;s the last story and what&#39;s closest to my mind now that I&#39;ve finished the book, but it made me think about my friend Justin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Book Review - 10% Happier</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/10-percent-happier/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 20:03:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/10-percent-happier/</guid>
      <description>Just finished 10% Happier by Dan Harris. I give it 3.5 stars, I guess. I rounded down on Goodreads and gave it 3.
The Good - I like personal stories, hearing about individuals personal struggles, how they overcome them, and how they have found ways to be a better person. As a parent I could use more mindfulness. A lot more mindfulness. It&#39;s a struggle. Maybe I&#39;ll start meditating. Anything I can do to help me reason instead of react is a good thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Favorite 2016 Books</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/2016-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 20:45:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/2016-books/</guid>
      <description>A few years ago I started reading a lot more and keeping track of what I&#39;m reading. I&#39;m a big fan of Goodreads. Anyway, something else I like are &amp;ldquo;best books I read this year (or last, as it were)&amp;rdquo; lists. So here is mine, in no particular order, except my favorite is first.
 Shoe Dog by Phil Knight  Fantastic book about the beginning of Nike. I don&#39;t care much about shoes, but I remember having Nike shoes in elementary school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World (again)</title>
      <link>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/hello-world-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 17:19:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://poorhoratio.com/posts/hello-world-again/</guid>
      <description>Let&#39;s see how many times in the next year I post something. I&#39;ll put the over/under at 2.5, not including this one.
So, the setup I am currently using is:
 Hover.com (domain registration) Cloudflare (DNS) Hugo (static site generator) Github pages  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>